3 York Place, York Street, Brighouse, HD6 3AL M: 07566208962 / E: robert.hemingway@live.co.uk

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a web developer with 5+ years of experience. I have a strong passion for technology and thrive in problemsolving situations. I am a clear and effective communicator able to understand both colleagues and clients requirements. I am hardworking and reliable, and I look forward to actively contributing to the overall success of a business I'm working for.

#### **EDUCATION**

2014-2017 University of Huddersfield

2:2 BSc (Hons) Computing

2011-2013 Rastrick Sixth Form College

A levels: IT, Maths & Business

Achieving an A grade in IT inspired me to apply for Computing at

university.

2006-2011 Rastrick High School

10 GCSE's, graded A-C including Maths and English

### RELEVANT EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# **2021-Present** Vizulate – Junior Developer to Developer

- Implementing majority of existing client work and updates
- Creating new websites for clients as part of a team
- Consistently developing and improving custom built WordPress themes, depending on the requirements
- Looking after majority of the hosting offered
- In some cases, be the clients main contact
- Being a guide for other members of the team

# 2018-2021 LSi Ltd – Junior Web Designer

- Creating internal basic websites that help aid other departments of the business
- Automating other aspects of the business to help free up time
- Partly working on large customer websites, aiding the Senior Developer where he saw fit
- Building basic WordPress WooCommerce sites to open up another avenue of sales for the business
- Learning other useful skills to a moderate level, such as Microsoft Excel & Google Sheets

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, PHP, CSS, JavaScript

CMS/Frameworks/Libraries/Other: WordPress, Laravel, Tailwind, Bootstrap, SQL, Git

## **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

I have a keen interest in music, listening to a variety of genres every day. I love to socialise with my friends and family, watching films and TV, playing pool, solving puzzles, watching an array of sports and helping other people.

I have also been doing small projects (websites etc) in my spare time over the years of learning web development.

### **REFERENCES**

Vizulate LSi Ltd

Jonathan Rich: Senior Developer Scott Brown: Lead Developer